The Sea to Sky Corridor could become the next hotspot for young independent travelers from Asia after being showcased by beloved Chinese entertainer and thrill-seeker, Wang Yibo.
凭借中国知名艺人、极限运动爱好者王一博的镜头推介，加拿大海天走廊或将成为亚洲年轻自由行游客的新晋热门目的地。
If all goes according to plan, there may soon be more tourists from China visiting Squamish.
若一切顺利，未来将会有更多中国游客前往斯阔米什游玩。
after a promotion of the district through uber popular Chinese celebrity Wang Yibo.
当地借助人气艺人王一博完成宣传推广后，热度持续攀升。
Destination BC’s China branch partnered with the outdoor documentary series “Exploring the Unknown with Wang Yibo” (Season 2) to showcase Squamish to millions of Asian viewers.
不列颠哥伦比亚省旅游局中国分部携手户外纪录片《探索未知》第二季，向数百万亚洲观众展示斯阔米什的风光。
For those unfamiliar with Yibo, he is a widely recognized celebrity in China. The 28-year-old is an actor, singer, dancer and professional motorcycle racer.
或许有人对他不甚了解：王一博是中国家喻户晓的艺人，这位28岁的艺人身兼演员、歌手、舞者与职业摩托车赛车手多重身份。
He is also a former member of the boy band UNIQ.
他也曾是男子组合UNIQ的成员。
Episodes three through six of the docu-series were filmed in Squamish and featured Yibo doing outdoor adventures such as aided and French free-climbing at Smoke Bluffs Park, deep-water soloing, stand-up paddleboarding, disc golf, and sea fishing.
纪录片第三至第六集取景于斯阔米什。王一博在烟崖公园体验了器械辅助攀岩、法式自由攀岩、深水徒手攀岩、立式单桨冲浪、飞盘高尔夫以及海钓等多项户外项目。
In August there were social media posts with suspected sightings around town such as at the Ark Tarricks Climbing Academy, but the production team kept the summer visit officially under wraps until the release of the series in the fall.
今年八月，就有网友在当地阿克塔里克攀岩学院等地拍到他的身影，但摄制组一直对此行低调保密，直到秋季纪录片正式上线才对外公布。
Monica Leeck, market development manager for Destination BC told The Squamish Chief it was an exciting collaboration for B.C. tourism and a way to promote the Sea to Sky and Squamish as a place to travel in other seasons.
不列颠哥伦比亚省旅游局市场拓展经理莫妮卡·李克在接受《斯阔米什领袖报》采访时表示，此次合作对当地旅游业意义重大，也能推动海天走廊与斯阔米什成为全季旅游目的地。
“Squamish is a year-round destination, there's many things to offer for different types of travellers. I think what is great about Mr. Yibo’s episodes will attract probably a younger, more independent-style traveller,” she said.
“斯阔米什四季皆可游玩，能满足不同游客的需求。王一博参与拍摄的内容，想必会吸引更多年轻的自由行游客前来。”她说道。
But also there's a number of amazing paid attractions in the Squamish area.
此外，斯阔米什还有不少优质的收费游玩项目。
Season 2 premiered exclusively on Tencent Video on Nov. 28, 2025. They are also great for small group tours or families etc.
《探索未知》第二季于2025年11月28日在腾讯视频独家首播，这里也十分适合亲友小团体与家庭出游。
So we'll leverage all of that information so that we can create a kind of a broader story about the destination.
我们也会借助此次热度，全方位打造当地旅游名片。
Exploring the unknown is co produced by Tencent Video and Warner Brothers Discovery.
《探索未知》由腾讯视频与华纳兄弟探索集团联合制作。
According to Destination BC within 30 minutes of the series launch it topped multiple popularity charts and surpassed 100 million views within eight hours.
据不列颠哥伦比亚省旅游局数据，纪录片上线30分钟便登顶多平台热度榜单，开播8小时播放量破亿。
The series is scheduled for international distribution via Discovery TV channels this year.
该纪录片计划于今年通过探索频道面向全球播出。